Puzzles:
  Chemistry:
    - question: "What is the chemical name for salt?"
      answer: "Sodium Chloride"
    - question: "How many electrons does Lead have?"
      answer: "82"
    - question: "How many neutrons does hydrogen have?"
      answer: "0"
    - question: "What is the chemical formula of Hydrogen Chloride?"
      answer: "HCl"
    - question: "What element is labeled K on the periodic table?"
      answer: "Potassium"
    - question: "How many electrons does helium have?"
      answer: "2"
    - question: "What is the chemical formula for water?"
      answer: "H2O"
    - question: "How many degrees is the melting point of salt?"
      answer: "98"
    - question: "True or False: Hydrogen is the lightest element."
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "What is the atomic number for Carbon?"
      answer: "6"
    - question: "What color is Au?"
      answer: "Gold"

  History:
    - question: "Who was the 16th president of the United States?"
      answer: "Lincoln"
    - question: "How many states are in the USA?"
      answer: "50"
    - question: "When was the Constitution written?"
      answer: "1787"
    - question: "Who was the first president of the USA?"
      answer: "Washington"
    - question: "What president was in a Wheelchair?"
      answer: "Roosevelt"
    - question: "What month is Independence Day?"
      answer: "July"
    - question: "How many crates of tea were poured in the Boston Tea Party?"
      answer: "342"
    - question: "What year did the Civil War start?"
      answer: "1861"
    - question: "How long did World War I last for?"
      answer: "4"
    - question: "How long did World War II last for?"
      answer: "6"
    - question: "How long was the Cold War?"
      answer: "45"
    - question: "Who was the 44th President?"
      answer: "Obama"

  Health:
    - question: "Rearrange the letters into a word that describes eating healthy: TRNITOIUN"
      answer: "Nutrition"
    - question: "How many hours of sleep does an average adult need per day?"
      answer: "9"
    - question: "True or false: Is water good for you?"
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "How many categories are in the food pyramid?"
      answer: "5"
    - question: "What is the smallest category in the food pyramid?"
      answer: "Fats"
    - question: "What is the largest category in the food pyramid?"
      answer: "Grains"
    - question: "How many servings should you have for vegetables?"
      answer: "3"
    - question: "What is the daily recommended serving amount for fruits?"
      answer: "2"
    - question: "True or False: Are nuts a part of the vegetable group?"
      answer: "FALSE"
    - question: "Write out the incomplete word: Physical T___apy"
      answer: "Therapy or Physical Therapy"
    - question: "True or False: Eustress is positive stress"
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "True or False: Protein is a macronutrient"
      answer: "TRUE"

  Math:
    - question: "What is the square root of 4?"
      answer: "2"
    - question: "What is the square root of 169?"
      answer: "13"
    - question: "What is 12 x 12?"
      answer: "144"
    - question: "What is the square root of 64?"
      answer: "8"
    - question: "What is 9 x 9?"
      answer: "81"
    - question: "What is the square root of 100?"
      answer: "10"
    - question: "What is 5x5?"
      answer: "25"
    - question: "What is 75/5?"
      answer: "15"
    - question: "What is 12x5?"
      answer: "60"
    - question: "What is the square root of 169?"
      answer: "13"
    - question: "What are the first six digits of PI"
      answer: "3.14159"

  IT:
    - question: "A blueprint which describes methods, functions, and constructors"
      answer: "class"
    - question: "A one-bit value (one digit) represented true or false, 1 or 0"
      answer: "boolean"
    - question: "A unit of measurement of information, 0 & 1 create digits known as the binary number system."
      answer: "bit"
    - question: "A collection of a fixed number of components wherein all of the components have the same data type."
      answer: "array"
    - question: "Write out the incomplete word: Software D____opment."
      answer: "development"
    - question: "What is the data type that represents a single letter or character symbol?"
      answer: "char or varchar"
    - question: "What is the primitive java variable that represents a non-decimal number?"
      answer: "int"
    - question: "A variable declared within the opening and closing parenthesis of a method signature is called a ____."
      answer: "parameter"

  English:
    - question: "Rearrange these letters into a word that describes an action in the sentence: VBER"
      answer: "VERB"
    - question: "Name an anagram for: PART"
      answer: "TRAP or TARP"
    - question: "True or False: MLA is a common format for writing essays"
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "What character or symbol is used for conjunctions?"
      answer: "apostrophe or ' '"
    - question: "True or False: The Great Gatsby novel was released in 1985"
      answer: "FALSE"
    - question: "Rearrange these letters into a word that defines a figure of speech: EMTPAOHR"
      answer: "metaphor"
    - question: "Write out the incomplete word: T__is Statement"
      answer: "Thesis statement or thesis"

  Business:
    - question: "Who is responsible for the overall direction of the company?"
      answer: "Top Manager"
    - question: "Manager who makes detailed schedules and operating plans?"
      answer: "First-line Manager"
    - question: "Who is the Father of Scientific Management?"
      answer: "Frederick Taylor"
    - question: "Who came up with the Hawthorne Effect?"
      answer: "Elton Mayo"
    - question: "What is a written document setting out business goals and how these will be achieved?"
      answer: "business plan"
    - question: "A purchasable physical item is known as?"
      answer: "good"
    - question: "A purchasable non-physical item is known as?"
      answer: "service"
    - question: "The existing successful business that is copied and used is called ______."
      answer: "franchise"
    - question: "A person who risks time and money to start and manage a business is called an _______."
      answer: "entrepreneur"
    - question: "The amount of money a business earns above and beyond what it spends for salaries and other expenses."
      answer: "profit"

  Nursing:
    - question: "Who was the founder of the American Red Cross?"
      answer: "Clara Barton"
    - question: "The theory of Human Care was Developed by?"
      answer: "Jean Watson"
    - question: "What is the ethical principle that requires healthcare and nursing to do good for others?"
      answer: "Beneficence"
    - question: "Negligence by a professional in healthcare is called?"
      answer: "Malpractice"
    - question: "Another term for a fever is?"
      answer: "Pyrexia"
    - question: "The part of the brain regulating the body's temperature is called?"
      answer: "Hypothalamus"
    - question: "Taking a pediatric patient to the playroom on a promised time and day is based on the belief in the ethical principle of?"
      answer: "fidelity"
    - question: "Who was the founder of the nursing profession?"
      answer: "Florence Nightingale"
    - question: "Respecting an elderly woman's decision to stay in her own home is based on a belief in the ethical principle of?"
      answer: "autonomy"

  Final Boss:
    - question: "What is 2 x 30 + 45 ?"
      answer: "105"
    - question: "True or False: The liver filters the blood in your body."
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "True or False: Python is a coding language."
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "True or False: The Industrial Revolution started in 1840."
      answer: "FALSE"
    - question: "True or False: A local area network is abbreviated as LAN."
      answer: "TRUE"
    - question: "What is the atomic number of magnesium?"
      answer: "12"
    - question: "True or False: abstract methods can be instantiated."
      answer: "FALSE"
